We learned one thing, Cheese:
我們學會一件事，吉事：
Cheerleaders and high explosives don't mix.
啦啦隊長跟強力火藥 不應該混在一起
You can say that again,Mac.
你說的沒錯，麥克
I couldn't have done it alone. You're a genius.
光靠我一個人是不行的 你是個天才
Oh,yeah? Well, how come I can't get my VCR to stop blinking 12:00?
是嗎？那為什麼我還不會調整 錄影機的定時功能
What did you guys think?
你們覺得如何？
-Hey,the phone. -I got it. I got it.
-有電話 -我來接
Hold on. It's your mom.
等一下，是你媽媽打來的
-It's Mommy. -That's nice.
-是他媽媽打來的 -真的是太棒了
Ma, so what did you think?
媽，你覺得如何？
Well...
喔…
that was okay.
還好啦
It wasn't the best.
它不是最棒的
That was one of the worst things ever...
那是我看過最爛的戲…
and not just on TV.
我是指所有的戲劇表演
-What should we say? -The lighting was okay.
-我們該說什麼？ -燈光還不錯
You got lighting last time. Lighting is mine.
上次你已經說燈光不錯 這次輪到我了
I have costumes.
服裝是我的
That means I'm stuck with:
那我只能說：
"So we were watching you in there,and you were sitting right here. Whoa."
「我們看到你在電視上出現 結果你就坐在這裡，哇」
-What about you? -I don't know.
-你呢？ -我不知道
I can't lie to him again. Oh,no,I.. No.
我沒辦法再騙他 不，我…不
I'm just gonna press my breasts up against him.
我要用我的胸部緊緊壓著他
-And say nothing? -Yeah,that's right.
-什麼都不說？ -沒錯
Wow, my folks really liked it.
哇，我爸媽很喜歡我的表演
What did you guys think?
你們有什麼看法？
It wasn't that good.
沒那麼好吧
The One With Rachel's Assistant
本集播出：瑞秋的助理
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Do you think that your favorite animal says much about you?
你認為你最喜歡的動物 能代表你嗎？
You mean behind my back?
你是指他們背著我說我的壞話？
You'll never believe what happened to me today.
你們一定不會相信 今天我發生了什麼事
-I am sitting in my office.. -You guys!
-我坐在辦公室裡… -大家聽我說
Guess what my agent just said?
你們猜我的經紀人說什麼？
-I'm in the middle of a story here. -Sorry,you finish.
-我正說話說到一半 -抱歉，你繼續說吧
I'm sitting in my office, and guess who walks in.
我坐在辦公室裡 你們猜誰走了進來
I'm gonna be on two TV shows.
我要參加兩出電視劇的演出
That's great.
那真的是太棒了
-Joey. -You weren't finished?
-喬伊 -你還沒有說完嗎？
Yeah, "Guess who walks into my office" is my story.
對喔，我的重點只是 「你們猜誰走進我的辦公室」
Ralph Lauren walked into my office.
勞夫羅蘭走進我的辦公室
If you're starting another story, at least let me finish mine.
如果你想說別的事 至少讓我把我的事說完
It's the same story.
我說的是同一件事
Wow, it's really long.
哇，這件事還真長
Ralph just came in to tell me that he's so happy with my work...
勞夫走進來告訴我 他非常滿意我的工作表現…
that he wants me to be the new merchandising manager for Polo retail.
他要我擔任 休閒衫零售部的新銷售經理
-Still get a discount on wedding gowns? -Yeah！
-你買婚紗還有折扣嗎？ -有啊
I'm so happy for you.
我為你感到高興
These really are the "days of our lives."
這真的是「我們的日子」
-What? -Well, since you ask...
-什麼？ -喔，既然你們問起…
They want me back on Days of Our Lives.
他們要我回去演《我們的日子》
I get a big pay raise!
我得到大幅度加薪
Oh,hey!
嘿
I'll be playing Drake Ramoray's twin brother, Stryker.
我要飾演德瑞克醫生的 雙胞胎弟弟史崔克
I get to hire my own assistant.
我可以僱用專屬助理
I got a head rush from standing up too fast.
我起來太快，現在頭很暈
You were at this job four years?
這份工作你做了四年？
-That's right. -This is all very impressive, Hilda.
-沒錯 -你的資歷非常棒，西爾達
I just have one last question for you.
我還要問你一個問題
How did I do? Was this okay?
我表現得如何？還可以吧？
-What? -I've never interviewed anyone.
-什麼？ -我從來沒有面試過任何人
I've never had anyone work for me.
從來沒有人為我工作過
When I was a kid we had a maid, but this isn't the same.
我小時候家裡有請傭人 但這完全不一樣
No, dear, it's not.
沒錯，親愛的，的確不一樣
And I know that.
我知道
Well, thank you so much for coming in.
謝謝你來面試
-Nice to meet you. -Good meeting you.
-很高興能認識你 -我也是
All right.
好吧
I'm a total pro.
我還真專業咧
-Hello. -Wow.
嗨
Hi, yes,I'm sorry. The models are down the hall.
嗨，對不起 模特兒面試在走廊盡頭的辦公室
I'm here about the assistant job.
我是來面試助理的工作
Really?
真的嗎？
Okay, well, then, all right. Well,just have a seat there.
好吧，我知道了 請坐
So what's your name?
你叫什麼名字？
Tag Jones.
泰格瓊斯
Uh-huh,go on.
繼續
That's it. That's my whole name.
就這樣，那是我的全名
That's your whole name. Of course.
那是你的全名，當然
Okay, let's just have a look-see here.
好了，我們來看一下
I haven't worked in an office before. I don't have much experience..
我從來沒有做過辦公室工作 工作經驗不是很多…
What are you talking about? You got three years painting houses...
你在胡說什麼？ 你當過三年油漆工…
two whole summers at TGl Friday's.
有兩個暑假在星期五餐廳打工
It's lame, I know.
那些經驗很爛，我知道
But I'm a goal-oriented person, eager to learn..
但我是目標導向的那種人 渴望學習…
Just hold on a second, please.
請等一下
It's for human resources. Everybody has to. Would you stand up?
這是人事部的要求，大家都得這麼做，能麻煩你站起來嗎？
No,no,no.
不
Hey.
嘿
-Anyway,I should go. -Okay. Bye.
-總之我該走了 -好吧，再見
-Hey,sweetie. -Hi,sweetie.
-嘿，親愛的 -嗨，甜心
What was with all the whispering?
你們嘀嘀咕咕在說什麼？
I can't tell you. It's a secret.
我不能告訴你，那是秘密
Secret? Married people aren't supposed to have secrets.
秘密？夫妻不該有秘密的
We love and respect one another too much.
我們深愛並且尊重彼此
But still,no.
但我還是不能說
We should tell each other everything. I don't have secrets from you.
我們應該對彼此坦誠一切 我就不會對你隱藏秘密
Really? So tell me what happened to Ross, junior year at Disneyland.
真的嗎？告訴我羅斯在大三時 在迪士尼樂園發生了什麼事？
No, I can't do that.
不，我不能那麼做
I'll tell you what Phoebe said.
我會告訴你菲比說了什麼
-Okay. -Okay.
-好吧 -太棒了
So Ross and I are going to Disneyland.
羅斯跟我 一起去迪士尼樂園玩
We stop at this restaurant for tacos.
我們在一家餐廳吃墨西哥卷餅
When I say restaurant, I mean a guy, a hibachi, and the trunk of his car.
事實上那只是一個傢伙 改裝了他的車子開的路邊攤
So Ross has about ten tacos.
羅斯吃了十個墨西哥卷餅
Anyway, we're on Space Mountain and Ross starts to feel a little iffy.
總之我們在玩太空山 羅斯開始覺得不舒服
Oh,my God. He threw up?
天啊，他吐了嗎？
No, he visited a town a little south of throw up.
不，他從另一邊 把東西全拉了出來
What was Phoebe's secret?
菲比有什麼秘密？
Nancy Thompson, from Phoebe's old massage place, is getting fired.
菲比以前的按摩師同事 南西湯普森被開除了
That's it? I gave up my Disneyland story for that?
就那樣？我為了那件事 說出迪士尼的秘密？
That's right. You lose,sucker!
沒錯，你輸了，笨蛋
Please still marry me.
請你還是要娶我
You have an assistant,right?
你有助理吧？
Did she call?
她打電話來了嗎？
You told her I was sick, right? Always tell her I am sick.
你告訴她我病了吧？ 每次都要說我生病了
I don't know. How do you decide who to hire?
不，我只是不知道 你怎麼決定要僱用誰？
I have it down to two people.
我把選擇範圍縮小到兩個人
One has great references and a lot of experience.
一個的推薦信很棒，經驗非常豐富
-And then,there's this guy. -What about him?
-還有另一個傢伙 -他怎麼了？
I love him.
我愛他
He's so pretty,I want to cry.
他帥呆了，我真的好想哭
I don't know what to do.
我不知道該怎麼辦
Come on, you know what to do. You hire the first one.
少來了，你知道自己該怎麼辦 你得僱用第一個人
Don't hire assistants because they're cute. Do it because they're qualified.
別因為他長得帥就雇他當助理 你得考慮到他們的工作能力
Uh-huh.
I hear you. You make a lot of sense. Can I just say one more thing?
我知道了，你說的有道理 我可以再說一件事嗎？
Look how pretty.
他真的很帥
Let me see.
讓我看看
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
Oh. But,no.
但還是不行
No. You can't hire him because it's not professional.
不，你不能僱用他 因為那麼做太不專業了
This is for me, yes?
這是給我的，對吧？
Okay,you're right. I'll hire Hilda tomorrow.
好吧，你說的對 明天我會僱用西爾達
Dumb, old, perfect-for-the-job Hilda.
那個又蠢又老，適合這份工作的西爾達
Let me see.
讓我瞧瞧
Wow!
Don't show this to Monica.
別讓摩妮卡看到照片
And don't tell her about the "Wow!"
別告訴她我說：「哇」
（我們的日子）
-Hey,Joey. -Hey,Terry.
-嗨，喬伊 -嗨，泰瑞
-Nice to see you again. -Been a while.
-很高興能再跟你見面 -好久不見
Funny,these halls look smaller than they used to.
真有趣，這裡的走廊看起來比以前小
It's a different building.
我們搬家了
So...
那麼…
Stryker Ramoray, huh?
史崔克是吧？
-When do I start? -How about right now?
-我什麼時候開始？ -何不現在就開始呢？
Okay.
好吧
Here are the audition scenes.
這是試鏡的劇本
I thought you were offering me the part.
我還以為 你們決定讓我飾演那個角色
Why?
為什麼？
I was Doctor Drake Ramoray, Stryker's twin brother.
我演過德瑞克醫生 他是史崔克的雙胞胎哥哥
Who looks more like me than me,right?
誰會比我長得更像我呢？
Everybody has to audition.
每個人都得參加試鏡
You know, Terry, I don't really need to do this.
你知道的，泰瑞 我真的不需要這麼做
I got my own cable TV series...
我有自己的第四台電視劇…
with a robot.
跟機器人搭檔演出
I'm sorry,Joey. That's the way it is.
對不起，喬伊 這是規定
Well...
那麼…
I guess you think you're pretty special.
我猜你以為你很特別
Sitting up here in your fancy, small-halled building...
你坐在漂亮的小辦公室裡…
making stars jump through hoops for you.
要大明星在你面前試演
Well,you know what?
你知道嗎？
This is one star whose hoop..
我就是那個大明星…
This is the star the hoop.. This hoop..
我就是試演的… 大明星試演…
I was Doctor Drake Ramoray!
我是德瑞克醫生
Hi,Tag. What are you doing here?
泰格，你在這裡做什麼？
I came to thank you for not laughing in my face yesterday.
我來謝謝你 昨天沒當著我的面笑我
I noticed there were no plants so I brought you your first.
我注意到你辦公室裡沒有植物 所以就幫你帶盆植物過來
There is a plant in your office.
你辦公室裡有植物
Kind of.
可以那麼說
Right.
對
So I guess I shouldn't put "good at noticing stuff" on my resume.
我猜我不應該在履歷表上寫著 「注意力敏銳」
-Thank you. -Anyway...
-謝謝 -總之…
I'm guessing you hired somebody.
我猜你錄取了別人
Well...
那個嘛…
Gotcha.
我猜中了
Thanks again for meeting with me.
謝謝你願意面試我
But I hired you.
但我錄取了你
-What? -Yeah, you got the job.
-什麼？ -對，你得到了這份工作
-You're my new assistant. -I am?
-你是我的新助理 -真的嗎？
Yeah.
對
-I can't believe it. -Me either.
-我不敢相信 -我也是
First, I need you to go downstairs...
首先我要你到樓下…
find a woman named Hilda, and tell her to go home.
找一個叫西爾達的女人 要她回家去
-Hey. -Hey, good you're home.
-嗨 -太好了，你回來了
Always nicer to hear than, "Oh,crap,you again."
我想這要比聽到 「該死，又是你」還好
Hey, sweetie, I made you a surprise.
甜心，我幫你準備了一個大驚喜
-Oh,yeah? -Yeah,tacos.
-是嗎？ -對，墨西哥卷餅
Ever since that story, I've had such a craving.
聽完那個故事後 我一直都想吃墨西哥卷餅
Did you not understand the story?
你聽不懂那個故事嗎？
-Hey. -Hey,what's up?
-嗨 -嗨，有什麼事嗎？
Nothing. Just figuring out what to do for dinner.
沒事 我只是想知道晚餐要吃什麼
Hey,what's that? Dinner stuff? You making dinner?
嘿，那是什麼？晚餐嗎？ 你在做晚餐？
No.
不
What's over there? Tacos?
那是什麼？墨西哥卷餅嗎？
No. No.
不
They're just ground beef smileys.
它們只是牛肉包大餅
Those are tacos.
那是墨西哥卷餅
Excuse me, Mr. Mexico.
對不起，墨西哥先生
Either way, I'll pass. Still can't eat those.
沒關係，我不吃了 我還是不敢吃那玩意
What's so funny?
什麼事那麼好笑？
I'm not laughing.
我沒有笑
You told her!
你跟她說了
Nancy Thompson's getting fired.
南西湯普森被開除了
Okay, okay. I had food poisoning. It's not like I chose to do it!
好吧，那時我食物中毒 我不是故意要那麼做
It's not like I said, "What would make this ride more fun?"
我又沒有說： 「該怎麼做才會更好玩呢？」
Right. You're right,I'm sorry. I shouldn't be laughing.
對，你說的對，抱歉 我不該笑的
I should be laying down papers for you.
我應該幫你先鋪好報紙
-How could you? -I had to. We're getting married.
-你怎麼可以？ -我非說不可，我們要結婚了
Married couples can't keep secrets.
夫妻不該有秘密
I guess Monica should know about Atlantic City.
我猜摩妮卡應該知道 在大西洋城發生的事
Dude!
兄弟
-What happened? -Chandler and I are in a bar...
-發生了什麼事？ -錢德跟我在酒吧裡…
Did you not hear me say,"Dude"?
你沒有聽到我說「兄弟」嗎？
and this girl is making eyes at Chandler.
有個女孩跟錢德拋媚眼
So he goes over to her and, after a minute or two, I see them kissing.
他走過去 一、兩分鐘後我看到他們在接吻
You're thinking he's not the type to go to bars and make out with girls.
你不會覺得他是那種會在酒吧裡 泡女人的男人
And you're right. He's not the type...
你是對的，他的確不是那種…
to go to bars and makes out with girls.
在酒吧裡泡女人的男人
You kissed a guy?
你跟男人接吻？
Oh, my God!
我的天啊
In my defense, it was dark and he was a very pretty guy.
我得為自己辯駁 那時很暗，而且他長得很漂亮
Oh, Mon, I laughed so hard..
老妹，我笑得很大聲…
So hard we had to throw out your underwear again?
你笑到又拉了一褲子？
Whatever, dude. You kissed a guy.
隨便你，老兄，你吻了男人
-Hi. -Hey.
-嗨 -嗨
How's Hilda working out?
西爾達適應的還好吧？
Oh,my new assistant is working out. Yes.
喔，我的新助理適應的很好，沒錯
She happy she got the job?
她很高興能夠得到這份工作嗎？
My new assistant is very happy that I hired my new assistant.
我的新助理非常高興 我僱用了我的新助理
Hello.
喂
Oh, hey! Can you hang on a second?
嘿，你能等一下嗎？
It's the producers at Mac and Cheese, if you'll excuse me for a minute.
是《麥克與吉事》的製作人打來的 麻煩你們先別說話
Hey,funny you should call. I was just looking over next week's script.
我沒想到你會打來 我正在看下星期的劇本
Canceled!
取消了
Like,they're taking it off the air?
他們不播了？
All right, I'll see you Monday.
好吧，星期一見
We're not even shooting them anymore?
不再拍了？
All right. Bye.
好吧，再見
They canceled Mac and Cheese!
他們取消了《麥克與吉事》
-Sorry. -Sorry, Joey.
-我很遺憾 -我真的很遺憾，喬伊
Why would they do that? It was a good show, right?
他們為什麼要那麼做？ 那齣戲很棒，對吧？
You want to tell secrets? Okay,in college...
你想說秘密嗎？好吧，念大學時…
Ross used to wear leg warmers.
羅斯都會穿衛生褲
All right,Chandler entered a Vanilla Ice look-alike contest and won.
好吧，錢德參加模仿香草冰大賽 還拿到了冠軍
Ross came in fourth and cried!
羅斯得了第四名，抱頭痛哭
Oh, is that funny? You find that funny?
那很好笑嗎？ 你覺得那很好笑嗎？
Maybe Chandler should know your secrets too.
或許錢德也應該 知道你的秘密
I already told him everything. You shush!
我已經告訴他一切了 你給我閉嘴
Once,she was sent to bed without dinner...
有一次她被罰不准吃晚餐…
so she ate the macaroni off a jewelry box she'd made.
結果她吃掉了 她用意大利面做的珠寶盒
Ross stayed home every Saturday night to watch Golden Girls.
羅斯每個星期六晚上 都待在家裡看《黃金女郎》
Monica couldn't tell time until she was 13.
摩妮卡到十三歲才會看時間
It's hard for some people!
有些人就是學不會
Of course it is.
那當然
Wow.
哇
-Chandler wore my underwear to work! -Hey!
-錢德曾穿我的內褲去上班  -嘿
I'm sorry,I couldn't think of any more for Ross.
對不起，我想不出來 羅斯還有什麼糗事
In college, Chandler got drunk...
在大學時有一次錢德喝醉了…
and slept with the lady who cleaned our dorm.
他跟打掃房間的清潔婦上床
That was you.
那是你
Whatever, dude. You kissed a guy.
隨便，兄弟，你吻了男人
How could this happen to me?
這種事怎麼會發生在我身上？
Yesterday,I had two TV shows. Today,I got nothing.
昨天我演出兩出電視劇 今天我什麼都沒有
Wait a minute, what happened to Days of our Lives?
等一下，《我們的日子》呢？
Well,they might be a little mad at me over there.
他們有點生我的氣
What happened?
發生了什麼事？
Well, maybe I got a little upset, and maybe I told them where they could go.
或許我有點太囂張 我告訴他們該怎麼做
Joey, why would you do that?
喬伊，你為什麼要那麼做？
Because! They wanted me to audition.
因為他們要我試鏡
You,an actor? That's madness!
你可是個演員，那麼做太過份了
Rachel Green's office.
瑞秋葛林辦公室
Tag.
泰格
Hi, who was that?
嗨，誰打電話找我？
Nobody. I was just practicing.
沒有人，我只是在練習
Really?
真的嗎？
-Hi. -Hi, Rachel Green's office.
-嗨 -嗨，瑞秋葛林辦公室
You must be Hilda.
你一定是西爾達
He's Tag. This is Phoebe. Phoebe, can I see you for a sec?
他是泰格，這位是菲比 菲比，你能進來一下嗎？
Phoebe.
菲比
-Great name. -You like that?
-這個名字很不錯 -你喜歡嗎？
-You should hear my phone number. -Okay.
-你應該聽聽我的電話號碼 -好吧，我們馬上回來
So you hired yourself a little treat,did you?
你為了自己僱用那個大帥哥，對吧？
I know how it looks, but I am telling you..
我知道這樣看起來像什麼 但是我要告訴你…
You can't get involved with your assistant.
你不能勾搭你的助理
I know that, and I know hiring him was not the smartest thing I've ever done.
我知道，我知道僱用他 不是明智之舉
But,from now on, I swear this is strictly professional.
但從現在開始 我發誓我們之間是純公事
-Yes. -Hey,Rachel.
-對 -嘿，瑞秋
Hi.
嗨
Cute assistant. What's his story?
你助理很帥，他死會了嗎？
-Is he.. -Gay? Yeah.
-他… -是同性戀嗎？對
Hey, Terry.
嘿，泰瑞
Joey Tribbiani.
是喬伊崔比亞尼
Surprised your big head could fit through our small halls.
我很訝異像你這樣的大人物 會到我們的小辦公室來
-I gotta go,Joey. -Wait,Terry! Look.
-我得走了，喬伊 -等一下，泰瑞，聽我說
I'm really sorry about before.
之前的事我抱歉
I was an idiot, thinking I'm too big to audition for you.
我是個白癡，以為自己很大牌 根本不必做試鏡
-Give me another chance. -I can't.
-再給我一次機會 -我辦不到
Wait,Terry, please!
等一下，泰瑞，求求你
Look,I just lost my other job, okay?
聽著，我失去了我另一份工作
You have no idea how much I need this.
你不知道我多需要這齣戲
Please, help me out.
求求你幫幫我
For old times' sake.
我們是老朋友了
This guy's been in a coma for five years. It's hopeless.
這傢伙昏迷了五年 他已經沒希望了
It's not. Dr. Stryker Ramoray is a miracle worker.
不會的，史崔克醫生擅長展現奇跡
Here he comes.
他來了
Good morning.
早安
Drake, it's your brother, Stryker. Can you hear me?
德瑞克，我是你弟弟史崔克 你聽到了嗎？
And cut.
卡
I'm back, baby!
我又回來了，寶貝
You know,in my defense...
我的解釋是…
there was no glitter on the macaroni and very little glue.
意大利面上沒有珠寶 而且我用的膠水很少
And in my defense, the cleaning lady came on to me.
我的解釋是 那個清潔婦勾引我
-Do you have trouble telling time now? -No.
-你現在會看時間了嗎？ -會
-Quick, what time is it? -Time to kiss a guy?
-快點，現在幾點了？ -吻男人的時間到了嗎？
What are you laughing at, Pampers?
你在笑什麼？尿布寶寶
You know when I said married people...
你知道我說夫妻…
should share everything and not have any secrets?
應該分享一切 不可以有秘密嗎？
-Yeah? -That was stupid. Let's not do that.
-怎麼了？ -那太蠢了，我們千萬別那麼做
Absolutely.
一點都沒錯
We should keep the stuff we told each other secret from everyone else.
我們不該把告訴彼此的秘密 再告訴其他人
Yeah,definitely.
一點都沒錯
Okay. If you'll excuse me...
好吧，對不起…
I'm gonna hang out with people who don't know the Space Mountain story.
我要跟不知道 太空山事件的人去玩了
-Then I'd steer clear of Phoebe. -Man!
-我建議你別去找菲比 -天啊
Not that you would, but I wouldn't hang out with the guys at my office.
一點都沒錯 我也建議你別去找我同事
Hi.
嗨
-Do you have a minute? -Sure. What's up?
-你有空嗎？ -當然，有什麼事嗎？
I got asked out twice today while I was at lunch...
今天我吃午餐的時候 有兩個人想約我出去…
by guys.
他們都是男人
-Really? -Yeah.
-真的嗎？ -對
Did you tell someone that I was gay?
你告訴別人我是同性戀嗎？
Oh,did you not want people to know that?
你不希望別人知道嗎？
I'm not gay. I especially wouldn't want you to think I was gay.
我不是同性戀，我特別不希望 你以為我是同性戀
Why is that?
為什麼？
-I don't think I should say. -Oh,you can say.
-我想我不該說的 -你說吧
Come on, I don't want you to feel like you can't tell me things.
別這樣，我不希望 你有事不敢告訴我
-Okay. -Okay.
-好吧 -好吧
-Well... -Yeah.
-那個… -是的
I'd love to ask out your friend Phoebe.
我想約你朋友菲比出去
Yeah, she's gay.
是啊，她是同性戀